I'm doing I'm I'm on top of the world
right now.
>> Good.
>> Congratulations.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Were you thinking you would get drafted?
>> Um,
you know, at the end of the day, you
know, I just I just knew that wherever I
end up, I'm just going to have to put my
foot down and, you know, get to work.
you know,
that that's just like I knew like at the
end of the day, at the end of today,
that I was going to know where I was
going to go and know what I need to do.
>> Was Atlanta on the radar for you?
>> Yeah. You know, I had a a great talk
with the coach Callahan um a couple
weeks ago and you know, it's honestly
such a blessing to be able to to work
with and to work with such a line
legend.
>> How'd that chat go, Ethan?
How' the chat go?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, it went great. Yeah, it went
great. You know, like we we got to
introduce ourselves to each other and I
really just got to understand, you know,
the culture that he brings to to to the
Falcons and just um you know, what what
he's trying to, you know, bring out from
his players.
>> I know you were at Rice and had a lot
looks like you had a lot of high
academic offers. I wonder what what did
you study at Rice and what what are you
going to do after football? So, I
majored I majored in bioeng engineering
at Rice and once like my PL career is
done, I would love to either go back
into medicine as a PA or work in
medtech, you know, on the R&B side or
work in medical sales.
>> Did you finish your bioengineering
degree at Ruckers?
>> Rice.
>> Rice. Did you finish your bioengineering
degree at Rice? Sorry.
>> No, no, not yet. So, I have um four
classes left, so I just got to knock
that out.
>> Four classes.
>> What are your expectations um coming to
camp, coming to training camp?
>> No, at the end of the day is really
just, you know, putting in work and just
improving every single day. You know, uh
a big thing for me is just having a
growth mindset. I just want to continue
to find ways to improve and, you know,
reach my fullest potential.
curious. Um, you played some, but
probably maybe not as as much as I
imagine you're hoping to at Ohio State
kind of how would you describe how this
past season went for you?
>> Honestly, I'll say is a blessing in
disguise that, you know, I'm truly
grateful for everyone that was at Ohio
State. I'm grateful for all the coaches,
for the staff, for the players because
at the end of the day, I chose Ohio
State because of those people. I chose
them because of the culture. I chose
them because of how the player how the
players actually buy into the culture.
And I chose it because of how the
coaches actually lead and you know are
about the culture. And you know even
though things didn't go exactly um how I
had planned, I still got better because
of it. I got to go against so many
talented players and you know I became a
better player and a better person
because of it.
>> Who I who challenged you the most I
guess maybe defensively in practice?
Honestly, it's it's hard to say because
I felt like the whole D line was was was
amazing. But, you know, like for sure
like you know, Kaden Curry, um Kayen
McDonald, you know, Arll, um Taiwan,
like they're all studs, and you know,
I'm truly grateful to actually know them
as as people and not just, you know,
players. And
>> when the season ended, like how did you
view your your prospects uh to get
drafted and to to keep going?
>> Honestly, as once the season ended, I
just knew it was time to work. Um I'm a
big believer in the the work is going to
is is going to show up you at the end of
the day. So the work that I put in is
going to result in um in in in the
fruits of my labor, you know. So
yeah, it really just like, you know,
grinding and just like finding ways to
continue to get better every single day
was just my mindset.
>> How would you outline the way that you
play, Ethan?
>> I'll say physicality is the biggest
thing and you know, just like always
being fundamentally sound. That's that's
those are the two biggest things that I
want to consistently show on the field.
I would imagine last year with the the
players around you at Ohio State, you
improved quite a bit. What areas there
would you say you could look at and say,
"Hey, I I grew a whole lot here from
where I was a year ago."
>> I feel like the biggest thing was
versatility um at Ohio State. That was
really my first time playing guard and I
was blessed to be able to play both
guard and tackle and on both the right
and the left side. So, you know, I was
really able to just kind of like expand
what I can do and I felt like learning
multiple positions really helped me
become a overall better rounded player.
>> Ethan, can I ask you what your shirt
says?
>> Um, it says guap.
Um, I'm not really sure. My um girl got
it for me.
>> Fair enough. You are a smart guy.
[laughter] Just wear Just wear the
shirt.
>> Yeah. I'm going just put on the shirt
and not ask questions. [laughter]